Obsession. Desire. Betrayal. How far would you go to hide the truth?
Broken Vows is a thriller film directed by Bram Coppens.
On her bachelorette-party weekend with friends in New Orleans,
Tara falls for the darkly-sexy bartender Patrick.
Waking in his bed the next morning, Tara instantly regrets her
unfaithfulness and flies back home to her fiancé.
But her secret flame becomes a full-on fire when Patrick shows up
at her house and begins stalking her every move.
He spirals into madness and delusion, determined to
have Tara no matter what the cost.
Tara, played by Jaimie Alexander.
Patrick, played by Wes Bentley.
Michael, played by Cam Gigandet.
Debra, played by Alexandra Breckenridge.
Annie Bloom, played by Emily Robinson.
Justine, played by Astrid Coppens.
Broken Vows is a 2016 American psychological thriller film directed by Bram Coppens from a screenplay written by Jim Agnew and
Sean Keller, starring Wes Bentley, Jaimie Alexander, Cam Gigandet, Alexandra Breckenridge, and Astrid Bryan.
The film explores themes of psychopath, new orleans,
louisiana, fiancé, one-night stand, stalker.
The tone is dark and intense.